

<u>Iazicn378@gmail.com</u>

Pančevo, Serbia

+381/65-368-3833

## **Profile**

I'm a dedicated Full stack software developer, specializing mostly in C#, ASP.NET, Javascript, Angular, SQL Databases, and I also write PHP / Laravel code. Currently, I'm on final year on ICT College, Belgrade. For the past 3.5 years I'm actively learning programming. I'm a hardworking person, and I love working in team since I have 4 years of working experience outside of programming. I have just finished 4 months internship for specialization in ASP.NET and Angular.

Currently I'm actively reading software engineering books such as "Head first design patterns" and "Clean Code" so that i keep improving my knowledge in software engineering and development.

# **Employment History**

### Laravel Backend Developer, IT Development Solutions, Pančevo

April 2022 — May 2022

- · Worked to meet client deadlines.
- Effetively multitasked and worked well with internal and external teams.
- Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, database design, and performance.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.

# **Internships**

#### Software Developer, Quadro Consulting, Belgrade

May 2022 — September 2022

Improving Angular and ASP.NET Core skills on 4 months internship. Mostly creating API, calling SQL procedures, using CQRS Pattern, SOLID principles and more.

## Education

## ICT College, Belgrade

October 2019 — December 2022

Department for Internet Technologies - Web Programming, software engineering

### Skills

C# .NET	ASP.NET
ASP.NET Core	ASP.NET API
JavaScript	Angular 2+
SQL Databases	SQL Server
Entity Framework	SOLID
HTML5	CSS3

PHP	Laravel Framework	
Bootstrap 4, 5		
Links		
<u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u>		
Courses		
C# Intermediate, Udemy		
Javascript Intermediate, Udemy		
HTL Leonding C# Course (2020/21), Rainer Strompek, YouTube		
HTL Leonding Programming Course (2021/22), Rainer Stropek, YouTube		

English

Languages

Serbian

German